[Theme song]
[nervous music]
[screaming]
[Surprised together]
(Hocheol)
Byun, lawyer, I…
[People screaming]
Please save me
[gunshot]
[Hanseo’s scream]
[Seunghyuk’s frightened groan]
[gunshot]
[Meaningful music]
[screaming]
[Seunghyuk’s frightened groan]
[Hanseo’s frightened groan]
(Chinese book)
Please save me!
[Myunghee’s frightened groan]
[Music that heightens the mood]
[gunshot]
What killed my mother
It wasn't an evil thing, it was the worst kind of foolishness.
[Myunghee’s trembling breathing]
(Vincenzo)
You killed so many people
Even though I know you tried to kill me too
Do you know why I didn't kill you?
[Seunghyuk’s heavy breathing]
Because it's annoying
[heavy music]
[shaking breathing]
I have work to do
If I kill you for no reason
Too many annoying things happen
Killing those little bugs is
It doesn't matter though
Anyway
You have to die now
[People moan in horror]
(Chinese book)
No, I really, no, I really…
[Seunghyuk is crying]
(Vincenzo)
Don't be scared
Because not today
[shaking breathing]
[Hanseo chuckles]
I have one principle
A painless death is a blessing
[laughter]
I'm going to give you two things from now on
A shame worse than death
and
Slowly feeling the stages of pain
death
[Seunghyuk’s heavy breathing]
(Vincenzo)
You guys take care of that trash.
and to me
Don't even think about blaming me
Who ordered it?
Because it will be revealed together
[Seunghyuk’s faint groan]
(Vincenzo)
Ah
[nervous music]
[Junwoo’s heavy breathing]
[Loads the gun]
There should be appetizers though.
[shaking breathing]
[gunshot]
[Junwoo’s scream]
[Music that heightens the mood]
[Junwoo’s painful moans]
[Myunghee’s surprised gasp]
(Myunghee)
Chairman!
Chairman, Chairman, Chairman
[Junwoo’s painful moans]
- (Seunghyuk) Oh, Chairman!
- (Hanseo) Brother, brother!
[Seunghyuk mutters]
(Seunghyuk and Myunghee)
119, 119!
[Junwoo’s groans with difficulty]
[Calm music]
(employee)
I will take you now.
Wait a minute
[shaking breathing]
[Sobbing]
[Crying]
mom
[Sobbing]
[Calm music]
mom
[Vincenzo sobs]
[Sobbing]
(Vincenzo)
mom
[Vincenzo sobs]
[Vincenzo’s crying]
mom
[Monks chant Buddha]
[The sound of a wooden table rings]
(Vincenzo)
The son I met after 30 years
All I gave my mother was death
If you hadn't met me
You would have lived longer
In the end I ended up living in hell
In the hell of regret
no
(Chayoung)
Although it was only for a moment
The lawyer told my mother
I gave you eternal heaven
My mother also gave heaven to the lawyer.
When the pain goes away, you will feel it.
But the most hellish thing is
I miss you already
mother
[Calm music]
[sigh]
[Vincenzo sobs]
(Gyeongja)
Lawyer
When I die, I will take this scarf
To our Joohyung
Please pass it on to me instead.
My ugly mother will leave it to the end
I only have a small scarf like this
It's so embarrassing
and
Please tell me this too
Joohyeong, you are
It was a blessing and happiness to someone
It was the only hope that kept me alive.
I felt the fetus moving in my stomach
From that moment until now
Not even for a moment
I never stopped loving you
Because I couldn't love you until the end
I was so sorry
my baby
Our Joohyung
I really love you so much
Thank you for coming as my son
I'm sorry
[Sobbing]
(Gyeongja)
Please take care of Joohyung.
thank you
[Vincenzo continues to sob]
[Junwoo groans in pain]
[The tweezers fall off]
Go and call your doctor right now.
(Junwoo)
Right now!
[Nurse's urgent breathing]
Get me discharged quickly
Brother, that
No matter what you do, it's going to hurt
Please be patient.
[Meaningful music]
(Junwoo)
Attorney Choi
Go and kill Vincenzo right now.
Whether it’s 100 or 200 people!
Mobilize and kill him.
Because it’s okay to spend as much money as you want
Huh?
Please fix it
Wound treatment comes first
(Junwoo)
I said I don’t need it!
[Junwoo kicks the cart]
(Myunghee)
Even if you don’t say anything
I will definitely kill Vincenzo.
[Meaningful music]
Now is the time to think about barbell first.
(Junwoo)
instead
just don't kill
Let us die in the same painful way.
Of course
[Meaningful music]
[Dark sound effect]
[gunshot]
[Vincenzo clicks his lighter]
[Dark sound effect]
(Vincenzo Wool)
mold
(Gyeongja)
Joo Hyung-ah
[Calm music]
[Soothing music cuts off]
[Lonely music]
[Dove cries]
[Clicks open the bag]
[Calm music]
[Closes the bag]
Just get it over with easily
What do you think?
Just Chairman Jang Han-seok and Choi Myung-hee.
I'm not looking for revenge
I started playing chess
[Vincenzo clangs his gun]
[Putting down the gun]
I'm going to move my phone one space today.
(President Cho)
Okay
Preparations are almost complete
[Meaningful music]
[sigh]
“Business closed”
(Heesu)
Lawyer
[Calm music]
Tsk, us.
I closed the business for a while.
(Larry Kang)
Smashing the barbell
I'm trying to help in earnest.
Now we really are a team
(Toto)
That fact
If you get angry once, everyone gets scared.
I will also do my best
(Cheolwook)
Because it is our collective decision
Please know that
Because I'm waiting anytime
If you need anything, please let me know
I'm still in the early stages of pregnancy so I feel light.
I can help
[Yeonjin’s laughter]
(Seokdo)
You know I come from a field workforce background.
Take it and use it anytime
(Heesu)
In the meantime
I thought we were the underdogs
not the weak
They were people who didn't want to become strong.
Now I'm going to go out a little harder.
Let us fight together
(Kiseok)
Lawyer
All of us
This is the Cassano family.
[Calm music]
(Cheolwook)
Vincenzo Cassano!
[A knocking sound is heard]
[The door clicks open]
(Chinese book)
Brother, let’s just rest today.
We'll finish it
Today is the last feeding day.
I should be there
[Door sound is heard]
[Seunghyuk’s faint groan]
(Myunghee)
Only local people from Sangcheon-gu
You don’t have to go.
(Seunghyuk)
Yes, the pledge too
We will handle it neatly.
Why is there so much talk?
I said I was going.
So, I said you were going, I
[cell phone vibrating sound]
“Vincenzo”
Did you have a good time at your mother’s funeral?
(Chinese book)
Vincenzo, Vincenzo, Vincenzo
Vincenzo, Vincenzo
[Meaningful music]
thanks
Is there any problem with your hearing?
uh
Thanks to you for shooting well
But
Is today the day I die?
You said I would give you something before you die?
(Junwoo)
I don't remember much
[laughter]
I shot my ear and it looks like my brain was injured.
(Vincenzo)
A shame worse than death
To give you this I
Starting today, I will play chess with you.
[Picks up a chess piece]
and hear your words
I will destroy them one by one
You are the only remaining chessboard
[laughter]
Aren’t you embarrassed and scared just thinking about it?
(Junwoo)
no
When it comes to chess, I have no intention of losing.
unfortunately
Your defeat has already begun
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Meaningful music]
[Italian]
Defeat is
It begins with fear
[Call end sound]
[laughter]
(Chinese book)
[Korean]
Brother, Vincenzo, Vincenzo
What does Vincenzo say?
Quickly move the miniature
(Chinese book)
yes
[Myunghee takes a breath]
Just bland
I couldn't have called, huh?
So, this
Isn't this something happening again?
(Seunghyuk)
Uh, tsk tsk, uh, no, tsk tsk
Well, well, well, always
Well, what's going on, what?
Tsk, yeah
[Hanseo’s disapproving groan]
Ah
[laughing awkwardly]
Ah, this precious thing
(Chinese book)
Ah, Choi Byun, please move it together…
[Hanseo’s disapproving groan]
[Seunghyuk’s awkward laugh]
(Seunghyuk)
How do you hear this?
(Chinese book)
I need to push this, why listen
[Seunghyuk’s elasticity]
- (Hanseo) Take out the code, take out the code
- (Seunghyuk) Oh, take out the code, code, code
[Interesting music]
[Seokdo rustles the candy]
[Cheolwook sighs]
(Seokdo)
Mr.
[Cheolwook rustles the candy]
(Toto)
Tsk, well, we could have been helpful.
how much will it cost
Even if I can't help you
All we had to do was convey our sincerity.
Is there anything else I can help you with?
Let's do some research
(Kiseok)
What's going on?
(Hongsik)
Wave your credit card and draw?
For the welfare of the family
Attorney Vincenzo gave it to me.
Family?
Everyone, please follow me to the department store.
Why the department store?
(Joosung)
I'm going to buy the Cassano family uniform.
[upbeat music]
[laughter]
(Chayoung)
Babel Tower licensing process
It's really a mess even when I look at it again.
[Vincenzo laughs slightly]
(Vincenzo)
It's not a mess
This is, well, almost like a graffiti.
Huh?
[Chayoung’s moans of denial]
[Vincenzo laughs]
Manager, after analyzing the guillotine file,
I think there will be more messed up things coming out.
Let’s take down the Tower of Babel
more trash
It would be nice to bury it in there, well.
[Meaningful music]
[Savoring moans]
[Car door slams shut]
(Chinese book)
Oh, hello, yeah
yes
- (Guest 1) Ahyu, Vice President
- (Hanseo) Ah, director, yes
[Interesting music]
(Man 1)
The attendants were in the waiting room downstairs.
You can wait.
(Attendant 1)
What is it?
(Man 2)
Inside, the event will be held only for VIPs.
(Attendant 2)
Hey, I've never heard that before.
- (Attendant 1) Oh, really.
- (Attendant 2) No, what does that mean?
(Attendant 2)
Let's go, let's go, let's go
- (Man 1) Please get out of the way.
- (Man 2) Please get out of the way.
[People are noisy]
[radio operation sound]
(Vincenzo)
Everyone, don't get excited and stay in your seats.
We strictly control personnel.
[radio operation sound]
(Kiseok)
Yes, consiglieri.
[Elevator arrival sound]
(Seokdo)
Oh, ordinary people can't go in.
- (Seokdo) No, go down.
- (Hongsik) I’m sorry.
[Hanseo clears his throat]
Now
(Chinese book)
Hello, guests of Sangcheon-gu,
You've been waiting for a long time
I am in charge of hosting today’s event.
Babel Group's talented housekeeper
This is Vice Chairman Jang Han-seo.
[People cheering]
Yes, finally today
I promised you
I would like to give you a gift
right away
This is the Babel Tower pre-sale ticket, everyone!
[Hopeful music plays]
[Hanseo cheers]
Yes!
[People applauding]
yes, yes
Okay then, Chairman.
(Junwoo)
This is Jang Han-seok
Until Babel Tower was decided
The mayor here
Chief of Police
(Police Chief)
Ah, yes
[Police chief laughs]
(Junwoo)
Rep. Kim
(Rep. Kim)
This is Wookhyun Kim.
[Rep. Kim clears his throat]
(Junwoo)
Other Sangcheon-gu VIPs’ help
It was absolutely
Of course our Babel
I have to repay the favor, right?
(Seunghyuk)
Hey, but I always forgot and didn't ask.
[Junwoo continues speaking]
We have our share in the Tower of Babel, right?
It's noisy
(Junwoo)
Congratulations
(Chinese book)
Now, let's start the event.
Everyone!
[People cheering]
[Meaningful music]
(Chinese book)
This is the 92nd floor of Babel Tower Building A.
[Drum sounds play]
The winner is
Congratulations, Rep. Kim Wook-hyeon
[Hopeful music plays]
(Rep. Kim)
Ah! I became it, I did it!
[Representative Kim’s laughter in the video]
(Rep. Kim in the video)
I got it, eh!
(Korean language in the video)
Wow, you like it so much
[Applause from people in the video]
(Chayoung)
But these guys really
[Video sound continues to play]
There's not even an inch of embarrassment.
How could it be like that?
[Interesting music]
(Korean language in the video)
This is a penthouse.
Humans cannot overcome greed
Overcoming greed is
Only greater greed
(Korean language in the video)
A house with perfect views...
Yes, our district mayor.
(District Mayor)
Uh, building tax reduction.
Building tax reduction, yay
Chief
(Police Chief)
When demolished, uh...
Police support!
(Chinese book)
Police support during demolition
Count this, everyone, count this.
Is there anything else, again?
District mayor
(District Mayor)
Everything related to Sangcheon-gu
Uh, private business.
Babel Group Attracted!
(Chinese book)
Won!
(District Mayor)
Hey!
[The district mayor’s happy exclamation]
(Chinese book)
Our district mayor won!
(Seunghyuk)
This way, this way, yeah
Wow, really
It's so nice, ayu, I'm jealous, huh?
(Man 2)
Wait a minute
(Man 1)
What's going on?
[Meaningful music]
(Chinese book)
Now, you are the last winner of the day.
52nd floor
Congratulations
Chairman Ham Seung-hoon
[Chairman’s laughter]
Yes, congratulations, yes, yes
[Hanseo’s laughter]
(Seunghyuk)
Wow, you like it so much
(Chinese book)
Yes, dear guests.
This concludes the winning ceremony.
To commemorate today, a cake cutting ceremony was held.
Let's proceed
Our district mayor, Assemblyman Kim
And the chief
Please come forward
yes, thank you
What is that?
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Rhythmic music]
[Myunghee’s surprised gasp]
(Chinese book)
Where are you coming in?
[Hanseo groans in pain]
(Seunghyuk)
Hey!
What are you!
[People are upset]
(Hwang Gyu)
this is a bomb
[People moan in surprise]
(Seunghyuk)
Bomb, bomb?
I'm being threatened.
Attorney Myeonghee Choi
you need to help me
Do you know someone?
Oh no
(Myunghee)
I don't know
How dare you pretend to know something! Mr.
(Hwang Gyu)
shouting here
If anyone tries to run away
This bomb will explode right away
So everyone stay still.
(Chinese book)
Wait, wait, wait
Well, who on earth ordered it, huh?
(Hwang Gyu)
I don't know either
After being kidnapped
I am receiving instructions only by message.
and
[People moan in horror]
(Guest 2)
What is that?
- (Guest 3) What is that?
- (Guest 4) What is it?
[Timer operating sound]
[surprised moan]
(Hwang Gyu)
here
there is a bomb
[People are upset]
(Guest 5)
Looks like a bomb, that thing
(Hwang Gyu)
I do what I'm told.
From now on, just as I say
you guys have to
This bomb stops
(Chayoung)
It's a good start
[Meaningful music]
[Machine operating sound]
(President Cho)
It's over
(Vincenzo)
Act well so it doesn't look like a fake bomb
Yes, don't worry
Once this is over
you are free now
(Hwang Gyu)
yes
(Chayoung)
최명희 밑에 있을 때 받았던 모욕들
오늘 다 갚아 줘
(빈센조)
아, 그리고 파티 끝나면
바로 입금할 테니까
오늘 안에 이 나라 떠
(황규)
여기에 있는 사람들 모두
바벨타워 분양받고 작성한 서약서들
모두 폐기하고
장한석 회장이랑 관계를 끊는 것을
무릎 꿇고 맹세해야 됩니다
무, 무릎, 무릎을 좀 꿇어야 되니까
[사람들이 웅성거린다]
빈센조
(한서)
야, 너 이 새끼, 너 인마
너 그거 지금 장난치는 거지?
What is the bomb, in Korea, Mr.
Quick! The bomb is about to explode!
But something seems a little awkward?
(Seunghyuk)
Uh, uh, yes, yes, yes, yes
This, this, this looks fake, does this?
Those aren't auxiliary batteries.
That one? uh?
If you're kidding me
Stop it now!
For those who don't believe
Let me prove one thing
5 seconds from now
[nervous music]
That Babel Tower miniature is going to explode.
[People are murmuring]
5!
[Seunghyuk’s frightened groan]
(Hwang Gyu)
4!
[People moan in horror]
3!
2!
[Hanseo’s frightened groan]
1!
[Machine operating sound]
[Machine operation sound becomes faster]
[Meaningful music]
[screaming]
[People screaming]
[Hanseo’s surprised gasp]
[Seunghyuk’s surprised groan]
(people)
Open the door!
[people shout]
[People in the video are noisy]
Are you really dead?
I told you this before, right?
When the time comes
The hunting dogs that killed lawyer Hong Yu-chan
They say they'll throw you into the lion's cage.
Originally, the lawyer
I tried to press it
I think it would be better for me to do it.
(Chayoung)
Ah, yes
[Calm music]
[Chayoung’s groans of difficulty]
[Chayoung sighs]
[Chayoung’s labored breathing]
[sigh]
(Vincenzo)
Have you changed your mind in the meantime?
[Music that heightens the mood]
My resolve hasn’t changed.
I have to make an intermediate settlement and move on.
[A shouting sound is heard]
[cell phone notification sound]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Vincenzo)
The bomb inside the cake
This can blow up the whole room
[intense music]
[People are upset]
[shaking breathing]
(Seunghyuk)
I-I didn’t come?
What, what, what is it, what is it?
(Police Chief)
Me, me, bomb
It's blowing up the whole room!
[urgent breathing]
(Chinese book)
Brother, brother, this...
This is real, real, real.
[shaking breathing]
[Cell phone beeps continuously]
(Vincenzo)
For reference, this plan starts from the beginning of the party.
is being filmed
[shaking breathing]
[People are upset]
[Keyboard operation sound]
[Cell phone beeps continuously]
(Vincenzo)
As the dead man instructed
Please act quickly
[Cell phone beeps continuously]
Quickly find your pledge
Chew and swallow
And after revealing his affiliation,
Get down on your knees and swear
(people)
Oath, oath!
[People are noisy]
[intense music]
(Seunghyuk)
Hehe, spit it out, spit it out, eh, really
(Police Chief)
I, the chief of Sangcheon Police Station,
His relationship with the Babel Group
I pledge to cut off!
(Rep. Kim)
Rep. Kim Wook-hyun...
Relationship with Babel Group
I promise to cut off
Everyone be quiet!
(Police Chief)
Chairman Jang, just be quiet!
Are you going to kill us all?
[Everyone shouts]
(District mayor in the video)
The mayor of Sangcheon-gu also
To sever ties with Babel Group.
I swear, I swear
[The district mayor sobs in the video]
[Rhythmic music]
Babel Tower is now licensed
It will be easier to make it invalid.
[Laugh slightly together]
[The mayor sobs]
(Police Chief)
I swear, I swear
[The timer sound stops]
Oh! Timer, timer stopped!
[Cell phone beeps continuously]
(Vincenzo)
Thank you for your hard work
with your abilities
Today’s party will be like nothing in the world.
Please make it clean
Everyone can go out
Get out, get out, get out, get out
(Police Chief)
We have to get out quickly now!
[People are noisy]
Tongue, bro.
This, this, really, really this
This is something, something real
It really feels like something is starting
Shut up, please
[surprised moan]
(Seunghyuk)
Timer, Timer, Timer, Timer
[Timer operating sound]
The timer suddenly, suddenly
Chairman, Chairman!
[Frightened breathing]
[Seunghyuk’s scream]
[laughter]
[Meaningful music]
[Myunghee’s trembling breathing]
[Laughs slightly]
thank you
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
I won without even using the bishop yet.
[breathes and then exhales]
The party ended easier than I thought.
the second party
It will be much bigger and louder.
I will prepare well for the second party.
[The door bursts open]
[Seunghyuk sighs]
[The door slams shut]
- (Seunghyuk) Uh, uh, uh, uh, right? uh
- (Article) came out, yes.
(Seunghyuk)
Me, senior, senior, senior!
[Laughing]
hello
loyalty
(Director Kim)
Representative Han
[Laugh together]
No, what happened here from morning?
(Seunghyuk)
No, well, I wanted to see you, senior.
[Seunghyuk’s awkward laugh]
Hello old man, how are you?
[laughter]
Are you happy that your approval rating has gone up these days?
[Seunghyuk’s elasticity]
Well, because our senior is the kingmaker.
I will only drink 1,000 drinks for the elderly.
[Laugh together]
It's been a while since I came here
It just sounds strange, huh?
[Seunghyuk’s awkward laugh]
But what really brought you here?
Oh, that…
[Meaningful music]
Can I see you sometime?
Why the elderly?
I have something urgent to tell you.
I'll see you after the election, okay?
Because it is a very sensitive time these days.
It's about the guillotine file.
- (Hyeokpil) Prosecutor, prosecutor.
- (Myunghee) It’s a surprise!
[tire rubbing sound]
[surprised gasp]
[Unfastens seat belt]
Driver, are you there?
[Myunghee’s surprised gasp]
(Myunghee)
Oh, surprise, Mr.
[Myunghee’s surprised moan]
where are you
Did you suddenly appear like this?
sorry
I should have come to see you sooner.
Maybe you and Hwang Gyu?
Hit me for my betrayal
Was Vincenzo there?
That's why things went wrong...
sorry
[Meaningful music]
(Hyeokpil)
please forgive me
What is all this?
(Myunghee)
What kind of face are you wearing now?
You crawled here, huh?
I was out of my mind, prosecutor.
(Hyeokpil)
Please save me
Prosecutor, please save me just once.
Wake up, wake up
You see people, it's work, tsk
[Hyeokpil’s trembling breathing]
(Myunghee)
I have so much to tell you
You are a small bead
If you want to live, you have to blow everything.
yes
Let's get on, let's go have a drink.
- Attorney Hong Cha-young
- (Vincenzo) Where?
[Interesting music]
IC
(Vincenzo)
Oh, really
[Hanseo cheers]
[sigh]
you come to work
(Chinese book)
[Laughing]
I'm not good at hockey
Uh, huh?
The information I gave you, how was it, was it good?
[Vincenzo laughs]
Thanks to me, sale ticket party
You made a mess
It wasn't bad
Ugh, if it’s good, it’s kind of good.
Please do something for me
(Chinese book)
Wow, tsk
What should I do next?
(Vincenzo)
Soon on your side
There might be a change
What changes?
After losing big
Because power moves
(Vincenzo)
If that happens, report it to me.
The place is here
(Chinese book)
Because it's not difficult
But me too, let me ask you something.
You won't kill me, right?
[Embarrassed laughter]
[Vincenzo laughs]
Oh, I know, I know, ugh
I feel a little anxious for no reason
As long as you don’t speak informally to me from now on
[Puck hits the wall]
Hey, I'm not even wearing a helmet, why are you like this?
[Interesting music]
(Chinese book)
Why are you like this, yo, yo, you're surprised
(Vincenzo)
Are you doing well studying?
(Chinese book)
My eyes are really blurry these days and I'm dying.
I read a lot of books
(Vincenzo)
It's not guns and knives that protect me
It's my head
Keep in mind
Going
Hey…
(Chinese book)
Hey there
[surprised moan]
[Calm music]
[Hanseo clears his throat]
(Vincenzo)
Why?
[mumbling]
What?
What are you saying?
uh
Thank you, thank you
[elegant music]
For making me realize how stupid I am
[Hanseo clears his throat]
[Laughs]
(Chinese book)
Ha, really, the power is
Vincenzo
[Hanseo cheers]
[Italian]
thank you
[Meaningful music]
[Hyeokpil’s groans of difficulty]
(Myunghee)
[Korean]
Oh my, you're hurt a lot?
(Hyeokpil)
[in a difficult voice]
Please save me
What?
(Hyeokpil)
Please save me
[Hyeokpil’s groans of difficulty]
Do you still think of me as a pushover?
[Myeonghee’s powerful moans]
[sniffles]
[Hyeokpil’s groans of difficulty]
Take it and bury it
[Exciting music]
[Vincenzo clicks his lighter]
(Vincenzo)
Now you go out too
Fight for yourself
(Cheolwook)
please teach me how
We lack skills in that area.
(Vincenzo)
First of all, my opponent's weaknesses
Use it like a weapon
(Chayoung)
You have to be shameless at all costs
There's no need for courtesy
(Vincenzo)
Treat me like I would treat my parents' enemies.
Like I'll never see you again
(Chayoung)
The requirements are exactly
Never give in
The enemy's status is high
Never be intimidated
(Vincenzo)
strong
Be easy on yourself
[Interesting music]
[Video sound plays]
[The district mayor sobs in the video]
(Toto)
Not even a goat
Why are you handling paper so well?
Why are you doing this to me?
During the Babel Tower site selection process,
You know there were a lot of problems with the on-site inspection, right?
We need to reinvestigate, then.
(Toto)
Based on this, a complete reexamination of the license
(Police chief in video)
I, the chief of Sangcheon Police Station...
(Yeonjin)
No, it's not like I'm doing some kind of speech contest.
If you cry like this
Can’t you taste blood in your mouth?
(Police Chief)
What do you want?
(Cheolwook)
first
Police around Geumga Plaza
Deploy permanently and strengthen inspections
second
To Geumga Plaza residents
Awarding the Brave Citizen Award
[Police chief sighs]
[Congressman Kim’s cheers in the video]
[Awkward laughter]
What can I do?
Development project near Geumga Plaza
completely blanked out
I vomited up everything I ate at the barbell.
(Heesu)
Give it to Geumga Orphanage.
[Congressman Kim’s surprised groan]
If you don't want to be embarrassed
(Hongsik)
‘Babel Tower Helpers’?
[dark music]
What kind of gangster demolition service company is this name?
What about later?
What kind of yogurt is it called?
Next up is the freezer, you bastards.
Take a good look at my face
Geumga-dong Nutria
[intense music]
(Chinese book)
No, huh?
They say they are reexamining the license.
What is an idol, huh?
what are you doing!
Shit, shit.
Because I flipped it over a while ago
I'll do anything
sit down
(Chinese book)
Ah, yes
[Hanseo clears his throat]
When I got shot in the ear
The day I got shot by you also passed by.
[Meaningful music]
[Embarrassed groan]
Why are you talking about that again?
It's good to be alive, man.
(Junwoo)
Did I tell you?
It's just the two of us
It's the same bloodline
From your mom before
I have a favor to ask you
be nice to you
Because it’s okay if you don’t give me anything
Just ask me to take it away
Did your mom say that?
uh
(Junwoo)
But now you're smart too
I want to give you something
no
No, brother, I’m…
That's enough for now
(Junwoo)
Babel Bio
Take charge and launch it
You wanted to take charge of a subsidiary.
[Heavy breathing]
No, brother, I…
I have the ability to do that
I can't do it, bro.
(Chinese book)
and
What about bio?
This doesn't make sense.
Do it, man
(Junwoo)
I saw you doing it
I'll leave it to you whether it's pharmaceuticals or chemistry.
If you really want to
[Laughing]
제가 한번 해 보겠습니다
(준우)
일로 와
[흥미진진한 음악]
엘리자베스 홈즈처럼
[웃음]
(준우)
혁신적인 기업가가 되어 보라고
내가 백업해 줄 테니까
[한서의 웃음]
예, 형님, 저 진짜
열심히 한번 해 보겠습니다
형님 감사합니다
잘해 봐
[웃음]
[숨을 후 내뱉는다]
(박 의원)
아, 문제없다니까 그러네
[문이 달칵 열린다]
어, 그렇게 진행해
아이, 새끼, 진짜
[승혁의 긴장한 숨소리]
아유, 오랜만이네, 한 대표
(승혁)
안녕하십니까, 어르신!
[The door clicks shut]
(Rep. Park)
Oh, what about the old man, just take it easy?
Ah, yes
(Rep. Park)
Is everything going well for Idol?
(Seunghyuk)
Ugh, what can I say?
And remember it all
thank you so much
[Rep. Park’s laughter]
- Just sit down, uh.
- (Seunghyuk) Yes
(Rep. Park)
Ah, at the idol after-party back then
Dancing tango alone
Is it ‘Gondre Mandre’?
Ah, the junior who called me that.
how could i forget
(Seunghyuk)
Oh, my, my, I must be crazy.
[laughing awkwardly]
I did it again, what should I do?
Oh, I'm embarrassed, I'm embarrassed, really.
(Rep. Park)
Uh, yeah, uh…
Let's talk about the guillotine file.
[Meaningful music]
What happened?
(Seunghyuk)
yes, that
Really twists and turns
That wasn't enough, old man.
(Joosung)
Lawyer
guillotine file
Only the Babel related parts
I analyzed everything.
The most overlapping keywords are
Do you know what it is?
- Bribes or sex scandals?
- (Joosung) Ding!
It's real estate.
Oh, how did you know?
This is Korea
That's right
To be more precise, it is IUDC
IUDC?
What is IUDC?
(Chayoung)
Innovation City Development Corporation
developing urban real estate
This is an organization that supplies
You can feel it, right?
[Vincenzo’s elasticity]
(Vincenzo)
As expected, the main item of the Korean Cartel is
It's real estate, real estate.
(Joosung)
There is no place where IUDC is not inserted.
Babel was already in agreement with the IUDC.
(Chayoung)
Insiders, people in collusion with them
They must have made money by buying the land around Babel Tower.
(Joosung)
He, a strong candidate for the next presidential election
Isn’t there Rep. Park Seung-jun?
That nobleman also took a detour like this
I already bought the land around here 5 years ago.
[Chayoung laughs]
My brother-in-law is the director of IUDC.
- Brother-in-law?
- (Joosung) Yes
[laughter]
(Chayoung)
Ah, a real guillotine file.
I guess I opened it for no reason, huh?
It's truly infinite sweet potato root.
Something keeps coming together, keeps coming
[Vincenzo laughs slightly]
Our goal is only one barbell
Tsk
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
(Chayoung)
Where are you going?
Ah
Even our greed
Now I have to start organizing.
I'll be back
[Meaningful music]
(Joosung)
Lawyer, are you organized?
[The door clicks open]
(Rep. Park)
So
In the basement of Babel Tower site
1.05 trillion gold bars
There is a guillotine file?
yes
It's an Italian mafia lawyer
I'm in control
yes, that's right
Director Kim
(Director Kim)
yes
Isn’t this a very cartoon-like story?
(Director Kim)
Oh, that…
Well, it's true to some extent.
It is being confirmed
(Rep. Park)
yes
Whether it's politics or life
There's a lot of drama
All of these issues are serious, sir.
Babel Tower
guillotine file
everything
There are knives pointed at my throat.
[Seunghyuk’s urgent groan]
(Seunghyuk)
Elderly
I am for the elderly
I will become an impenetrable shield.
If you want to see that shield
How can I help you?
Elderly…
[laughter]
[Seunghyuk’s heavy breathing]
[Interesting music]
(Vincenzo)
I'm sorry to say it again, but
I'll take you somewhere else
please leave here
(dropping)
What are you doing this for again?
I was lucky last time
If another explosion occurs
This underground area is the most dangerous.
So you better get out of here quickly
It looks good
(Chae Shin)
Theravada and the head monk follow the Buddha’s will.
will continue to be here
Lawyer
yes
One at this point
I want to ask you something.
yes please say
[sigh]
[Exciting music]
Oh, are you really going to Babel Tower?
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
From what I hear
What, you said there was going to be a reinvestigation?
(Director Tae)
Well, in my experience
If I can’t get through this all at once,
[Meaningful music]
not easy to climb
(Director Cheon)
Each media outlet also said something was unusual.
words are coming out
(Chinese book)
Ah, everyone
This is just trivial
It's a document error issue.
It's not a big deal
(Myunghee)
within a few days
Our idol is going to solve it
[Director Tae clears his throat]
(Junwoo)
First, have a drink.
Although it is weak
Please check the gift
(Chinese book)
Oh my, I really
[Hanseo opens the case]
Everyone no, no
You know that, huh?
[Hanseo puts down his glass]
(Chinese book)
Ah, unlucky people.
Can't we just blow it all up?
(Myunghee)
Today’s members
These are greetings you cannot afford to lose.
Please keep soothing me
(Junwoo)
Even if it's not Bishop
Because they are people who have at least a phone.
[Myunghee sighs in frustration]
As expected, brother
Are you comparing the situation to a chessboard?
You are really cool
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Where are you?
[Meaningful music]
(Seunghyuk)
Uh, everyone went, right?
I have a customer right now
I'm trying to take you with me.
Guest?
I finally see you today
Mr. Vincenzo Cassano
Hello, Director.
[Director Tae holds hands]
(Chayoung)
This is lawyer Hong Cha-young.
Ah, the lawyer too.
I heard a lot of words
[Director Tae’s laughter]
(Joosung)
Director
Nice to meet you, office manager.
Ah, ah, yeah
[Joo Seong and Director Tae’s laughter]
[Exciting music]
(Vincenzo)
Ahn, I have something to talk about.
(Kiseok)
[in a trembling voice]
So
Ah, there, ah
[Kiseok’s heavy breathing]
Guy, the guillotine file to the consiglier...
Anyone who knows this fact
Me, Attorney Hong, office manager
There are only three
Be sure to keep your secret
Well, then, immediately become our informant…
No, not yet
There are things we can do with this.
Yeah, that's right
You can tie it all together with this.
(Vincenzo)
That's it
You believe me, right?
so much
If so, the guillotine file
Trust me on how to use it
After using it all
I'll hand it over to the informant.
Because I know how to use it
I believe in consiglieri
(Vincenzo)
thank you
[surprised moan]
First of all, I have a favor to ask.
Just say the word
[Interesting music]
(Director Tae)
Hey!
So the guillotine file
It's sealed in the basement of Geumga Plaza?
Who can take it out
Just Vincenzo Cassano?
yes
You bastard!
You to Vincenzo
There was a reason why you put in the effort.
[Director Tae’s laughter]
[Kiseok’s embarrassed groan]
Soon the guillotine file
I'll give it to the director.
- (Director Tae) Yes.
- (Kiseok) Then, Director
(Kiseok)
Headquarters Director Kim Hee-won beats Director Park Jae-beom
You become the director.
- Director?
- (Kiseok) Yes
[Overwhelmed moan]
[Interesting music]
Hee-won Kim, Jay-beom Park
[Laugh together]
Hey, how can I help you?
(Junwoo)
Now
Babel Tower Signature
Starting from the 120th and 121st floors
What is it?
(Kiseok)
First, infiltrate Babel Group.
Please find something that could be a weakness.
How to safely remove a guillotine file
You have to break the barbell first.
(Director Tae)
Oh, sorry I'm late.
I suddenly had an urgent meeting.
foreign security information source
This is Tae Jong-gu, director of the International Crime Response Bureau.
(Kiseok)
and the second
Vincenzo Cassano
Please don't let me touch you.
(Director Tae)
He, Vincenzo Cassano
This is someone you should never touch.
Yes?
(Director Tae)
Not only in Italy
British and French politicians
with negative evidence
He fled to Korea.
It was bigger than I thought, huh?
(Director Tae)
Yes, I write
If you die
Right on the dark web
I let the evidence spread.
If an international scandal occurs
Our government will not escape responsibility either.
[Music that heightens the mood]
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Video sound plays]
(Chayoung)
It's good
The clown is so explosive
(Joosung)
Hey, that little golden toad.
Huh? how much
[Director Tae’s laughter]
(Director Tae)
Even at the last meeting
I had a hidden camera installed.
It wasn't recorded
Well, Team Leader Ahn
Because I'm not good at explaining things
The director turned on and off in reverse.
(Director Tae)
Hey!
[Director Tae’s awkward laugh]
Well, anyway, thanks
I'm moving forward
I think I'm going to do big things
[Director Tae’s laughter]
Actually, more than me
Thanks to the person over there
[Exciting music]
(Vincenzo)
Yeah
Hello, Director.
(Director Tae)
no
Team leader Joe
[Laughs slightly]
No, why is Team Leader Cho here?
(President Cho)
Uh, let me tell you.
It's a bit of a long story.
(Kiseok)
Right, right, right?
President Cho, this is our company, right?
[Kiseok’s happy sigh]
As expected, it looked familiar
[Humorous sound effects]
(Chayoung)
Let's spread the word among people from the same company.
[Kiseok’s laughter]
(President Cho)
How old are you?
[Interesting music]
[Embarrassed groan]
No, Team Leader Ahn is higher.
(President Cho)
Ah, baby face
(Kiseok)
Attention, rest intently
- child
- (Kiseok) ‘Child’?
Concentrate
[laughter]
(Director Tae)
stop motion
(Myunghee)
This, this, this...
No, this, this
Does that make sense now, senior?
(Chinese book)
So, uh
Representative Han becomes the chief prosecutor of the Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office
[Meaningful music]
Choi Byun will just become CEO of Woosang?
It looks like you don't know much.
I am originally from the Supreme Prosecutors' Central Investigation Department.
[Embarrassed laughter]
(Myunghee)
You won one game and got kicked out, you
(Seunghyuk)
Me?
(Director Kim)
Oh, and
the italian mafia lawyer
Don't ever touch me
He's bigger than you think
An international problem arises
[Junwoo laughs]
You're a bit rude at first meeting.
Don't mind our business.
Giving another chance like this is also
(Director Kim)
Know with the generosity of elders
There's no need for tolerance or anything like that?
(Director Kim)
The person who killed my father by poisoning him
That's a lot to say, huh?
[Meaningful music]
Why did you think I didn't know?
[Embarrassed groan]
While we're at it, one more thing
Chairman Jang Han-seok takes a short break.
Vice Chairman Jang Han-seo
I think it would be good to become president again.
Yes?
Me, me, me?
(Myunghee)
Senior
Even though it is an order from an elder,
It's a bit weird to say this to the chairman of a private company...
(Director Kim)
Choi Myung-hee, Chairman Jang
When the regime changes
You should be fine, right?
And Choi Myung-hee, if you pout one more time
Approval rating: 38.7% On the path to becoming a presidential candidate
It is considered spraying thumbtacks.
[Atmospheric music plays]
[Seunghyuk’s elasticity]
(Seunghyuk)
Congratulations, Mr. Chairman.
Ha, one more time
Chairman
[Laugh together]
I really am the president again, the president…
[laughter]
I was making this picture
Do you know how hard it was for you?
Representative Han, no.
Brother, Seunghyuk
Hey, tsk
Chief Prosecutor
Chief Prosecutor Han Seung-hyuk
[Laugh together]
(Chinese book)
I really like this picture
It's so dreamy I can't believe it
He, he, he, who is he? Him?
What, Jang Jun-woo?
- Vincenzo
- (Korean book) Vincenzo
within 24 hours
Interpol is coming to catch you.
Interpol?
[Meaningful music]
- (Seunghyuk) Interpol, international police…
- (Hanseo) I know, I know.
(Seunghyuk)
Yeah
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
I am that
I spoke to the Cassano family boss on the phone.
I made a board
A charge that could be leveled against Vincenzo.
ask me for one
That's what I reported to Interpol.
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
[Elasticity of Hanseo]
Wow
[Hanseo’s laughter]
Hey, stop it.
No, why didn't I think of that?
Likely to have a guillotine file
Sending away the most people
(Seunghyuk)
Our president, huh?
After destroying Geumga Plaza
All you have to do is remove the guillotine file.
(Chinese book)
But
Vincenzo went there
Couldn’t it come back again?
[Seunghyuk’s moans of denial]
(Seunghyuk)
Hey, that's impossible.
Now our Chairman
Just guide the barbell well.
As for the rest, Chief Prosecutor Lee just supports you!
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
[Elasticity]
(Chinese book)
Jang Han-seok
[Refreshing moan]
Who is good at who?
[Music that heightens the mood]
[laughter]
[takes a breath]
[Exhales]
[laughter]
[Camera shutter sounds repeatedly]
(Reporter 1)
As the new district prosecutor
Please tell me one word of your resolution.
Being able to work for the people
I feel infinitely honored
[Meaningful music]
(Seunghyuk in the video)
I am
As a defender of the rule of law and democracy
[Vincenzo laughs]
The principle of justice in this land
So that I can stand upright
I plan to give my all.
[Reporter 2 in the video asks a question]
(Joosung)
Ah, really that kind of person
How did he become a district prosecutor overnight?
Jang Han-seok’s power
I can't make that much space.
It must have reached a much higher level.
to defend against our attacks
So what if?
But why doesn’t Jang Han-seo report it?
This important issue
That's right, I fell in love with it.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Vincenzo)
It's not gone yet
Uh, tell me
I have something urgent to discuss now.
[Meaningful music]
[radio operation sound]
(bodyguard)
We are leading you to Area A.
"Interpol"
[Greetings in Italian]
[You can hear people shouting]
What do you need to discuss urgently?
[Meaningful music]
[Hanseo sighs]
I'm really going crazy
[sigh]
[Siren sounds]
(Chinese book)
i
I suddenly had a problem
[nervous music]
What is it? tell me
[sigh]
Why is life like this
I don't know if it's a series of choices.
[Hanseo sighs]
(Chinese book)
We had fun so far
Something fun
I think it should end now
[Gun clangs]
[nervous music]
That brother and that younger brother.
Well, I wasn't expecting it in the first place.
[dark music]
Hey, the gun...
Don't shoot, I have a gun too
What I mean is that you betrayed me
It means that the purpose has been achieved.
(Chinese book)
Hey, if you shoot either of these
Because it's a big problem, just
Let's both lower our guns together, okay?
I don't plan on getting off?
Actually my gun has no bullets
It's just an empty gun
(Vincenzo)
Yeah
Then shoot yourself in the head first.
No! Oh no, no
I was just aiming to scare you.
Shoot first
(Interpol police)
Vincenzo Cassano!
[The door bursts open]
[Meaningful music]
[The door slams shut]
[Italian]
It's Interpol
(Interpol police)
arrest you and
I came here to repatriate you to my home country.
(police)
[Korean]
Throw away your gun
Mr. Vincenzo Cassano
[gunshot]
[nervous music]
[Music that heightens the mood]
[Magnificent music]
Subtitle: Kwon Jeong-won